northaware.com 2018-08-21

# Privacy Policy | North Aware, an Innovative Winter Coat Brand

North Aware can also be referred as "We" or "Company". 

**Introduction**

North Aware respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site, Facebook, our micro sites and splash pages hereby collectively called “website”, “site” or “we” in the ways disclosed in this statement.

We collect two types of information on our website.

a) Personal identifiable information

b) Anonymous information

**PartI. Collection of Personal Identifiable Information**

Personal Identifiable information is provided by you at several places on our website like when you create your account, send us an email, post on our website, link your Facebook account to the site etc.

This information includes, your full name, date of birth, address information including city, state, country, zip code and street address, email address, CNIC and your chosen password. This information is used to identify you and contact you regarding your account. We store this information in our database. 

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise share for marketing purposes the Personal Information that we collect with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

Your personal information stored in our database is accessible by our staff to provide customer support or to resolve any problems you have. Information may also be accessible by any reputable third party support companies to resolve technical issues or problems you may have.

**Sharing your Personal Information with Merchants**

Your passwords are encrypted and not even our staff can know your password. You are advised not to disclose your password to any third party in any case as only you will be responsible for any misuse of your account.

**Information Related to Minors**.

We do not allow anyone under the age of 13 to sign-up on our website. In case you are under 18 and 13 or above, you must have parental or guardian consent to sign up on we. We will never knowingly store personal identifiable information of anyone less than 13 years of age, and we do every effort to identify and delete such information from our database.

**Payment Information**

When you purchase a product, we may ask you to provide your credit card number, CVV code, expiry date etc. 

Your credit card information is never stored on our servers and is transmitted directly to the payment processor(s). Your credit card information may be shared with your card issuing bank for verification or with our payment processor and other companies used by our payment processor and the involved bank and it’s controlled by their respective privacy policies.

**Changing Personal Information**

You can log in to your account and change any personal information at any time by clicking “profile link” in your control panel. Even if you change your personal information, your previous information related to other activities may remain unchanged in our database. We also take backups of our database so it will not be possible to completely delete your information from our website.

**Business Information from Merchants**

From businesses, we may gather other personally identifiable information about the business and the owners/directors and employees of that business.

The information includes but is not limited to business name, type of business, years in business, tax id, address information etc.

**Part II. Anonymous Information**

We might also collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information. We collect demographic data in order to analyse our marketing results.

We collect this information through registration forms, click stream tracking, automatic logging files, Cookie, Pixel tags and so on. This information includes your IP address, Browser type, URL you were visiting before coming to our site, your referral ID, etc.

We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable us to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies do have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

This information is used to analyze user patterns, demographics etc. to better design our marketing campaign and to make our website more user friendly. The information may also be shared with our advertising and marketing partners to improve our marketing results.

**Part III. Law enforcement**

Your identifiable and anonymous information may be used and released to law enforcement agencies to protect our rights and security of our users. The information may be released to comply with the law and to cooperate with law enforcement agencies.

**Part IV. Security**

We take security of your personal identifiable information very seriously. Your passwords and other sensitive information is encrypted through SSL. All sensitive information is taken from users on pages secured by SSL utilizing 128 bit encryption.

Although we take all commercially reasonable security measures, it is not possible to guarantee 100% security of your data transmitted through our website as it is with any other website on the Internet.

You hereby hold us harmless of any damage, loss of property, claims, financial loss, loss or damage of equipment caused due to leakage of your personal information or by the actions of the third partied with whom we share your information to the extent of the applicable law.

**Part V. Comments and Feedback**

You understand that all the comments and feedback you post on our website are public and can be viewed by anyone. You hereby allow us to use your feedback and comments anywhere on our website without paying any royalties and compensation to you.

**Part V. Business Acquisition**

We may be acquired or merge with other business. In this case the successor company will have all your personally identifiable information and Anonymous information. The successor company however will be bound to treat your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Part VI. Changes in Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy can change with notice to you via email, or through notification on this page. In case of such change you will have the right to cease use of the site if you do not agree to the new privacy policy. You continued use of the site after 48 hours of such notice will mean you approval of the new policy.

**Part VII. Problem Resolution**

If problems arise, users may contact us through mail, email or phone. We try our best to resolving any privacy issues you have within three working days.
